Queen's Head and Artichoke UP207
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Queen's Head and Artichoke
1989 -- 2001
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UP207
0.5 Linear Feet
2 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Queen's Head and Artichoke. It is a student literary magazine, which includes such creative endeavors as short stories, poetry, art work and photographs.
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the pervue of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
- Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1989 -- 2001; 1989 -- 2000; UP207.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Queen's Head and Artichoke. It is a student literary magazine, which includes such creative endeavors as short stories, poetry, art work and photographs.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1989 -- 1990; UP207.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
    Volume
    1
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1990 -- 1991; UP207.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
    2
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1991 -- 1992; UP207.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
    3
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1992 -- 1993; UP207.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
    4
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, Fall, 1993; UP207.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
    5
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, Spring, 1994; UP207.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1994; UP207.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    6
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1995; UP207.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    7
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1996; UP207.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    8
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1996 -- 1997; UP207.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    9
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1997 -- 1998; UP207.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    volume #'s mis-marked
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1998 -- 1999; UP207.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    10
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 1999 -- 2000; UP207.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    11
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 2000 -- 2001; UP207.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    12
  - Queen's Head and Artichoke, 2001; UP207.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    13